<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>travel on 0x7CC</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/tags/travel/</link><description>Recent content in travel on 0x7CC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.brennan.sh/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Years 2019 in Japan: Part Two.</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/posts/japan-part-two/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.brennan.sh/posts/japan-part-two/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="tokyo-odaiba-and-onsens">Tokyo: Odaiba and Onsens&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Over the next few days I went to different shops, landmarks, and things that I saw online. Starting off the series of days with a visit to Tsukiji Fish Market and ate some of the the ever amazing Tuna Fish that it is famous for. From there I went off to start my adventures around Odaiba, an up-and-coming industrial/commercial section with massive buildings and a tonne of cool places to visit. Some of the cool places to visit are the Science Center, Team Labs Borderless, and the various statues and monuments.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/hakone.jpg" alt="Hakone!">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The day after Odabia, I spent a day trip to visit the Tenzen Onsen in Hakone, Japan. Of all the destinations I visited during this trip, this day was easily the most interesting and the most authentic insight into the lives of native Japanese. For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, an Onsen is a communal Japanese bath house traditionally that was filled hot water funnelled from volcanic hot springs, high in mineral content, for people to bathe in. Along with the beauty of the Onsen, the surronding town of Hakone was very nice. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure but if I had to guess, this is a very &amp;ldquo;Resort&amp;rdquo; area as the shops and resturants felt like they were built for that cause.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="tokyo-final-days">Tokyo: Final days&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The last few days I spent visiting other smaller destinations I wanted to hit as well as re-visiting the ones that I liked the best. Including Roppingi Hills, Shinbashi, and Ginza. Three of the wealthier destinations in Tokyo. While in Roppongi, I had one thing I truly wanted to visit and that was the maman statue by Louise Bourgeois. This statue is signifigant to me because I live in Ottawa, where one of the 7 perminant statues exists, and I got to travel to the other side of the world to visit another of the 7. I also spent many more hours and thousands more yen playing Ongeki.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="kyoto-lots-of-walking">Kyoto: Lots of walking&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Taking the bullet train to Kyoto was an incredible experience, going 300mph on land is terrifying but oddly serene and calming. I also managed to snag a seat with a view of Mt. Fuji. Unfortunately it was a bit cloudy and this was the best view I could get.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/fuji.png" alt="Hakone!">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Due to my over-stay in Tokyo, I only got a few days to spend in Kyoto but I tried my best to make the time I had. Most of the time on the first day was spend walking between the major sights and sounds of Kyoto. From the Golden Palace, to the Fushimi Inari shrine, and the Gion. There isnt much else to be said about my time in Kyoto, except to visit a bar called Beer Bar Jive. 10/10&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="food">Food&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>That wraps up my experiences in Japan, however here is a small gallery of all the food I got to enjoy.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/food/curry.png" alt="Hakone!">
&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/food/beef.png" alt="Hakone!">
&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/food/pancakes.png" alt="Hakone!">
&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/food/pastry.png" alt="Hakone!">
&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/food/bun.png" alt="Hakone!">
&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/food/takiyaki.png" alt="Hakone!">&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>New Years 2019 in Japan: Part One.</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/posts/japan-part-one/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.brennan.sh/posts/japan-part-one/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="the-flight">The Flight&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>My flight to Tokyo started in Nanaimo Airport (&lt;a href="https://www.flightradar24.com/data/airports/ycd">YCD&lt;/a>) for a quick hop to Vancouver Internation Airport (&lt;a href="https://www.flightradar24.com/data/airports/yvr">YVR&lt;/a>). I was lucky to find a deal from Vancouver to Tokyo on ANA which is one of the best airlines in the world, and it shows.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/food.jpg" alt="Eggs + Ground (pulled) salmon + shitakee mushroom cap, seaweed + Roe, Colslaw + Chicken">&lt;/p>
&lt;h6 id="eggs--ground-pulled-salmon--shitakee-mushroom-cap-seaweed--roe-colslaw--chicken">Eggs + Ground (pulled) salmon + shitakee mushroom cap, seaweed + Roe, Colslaw + Chicken&lt;/h6>
&lt;p>The service, food, and amenities provided by the airline were all at the top of their game. Even given the fact that the food was my first real taste of &amp;ldquo;authentic&amp;rdquo; Japanese food and it wasn&amp;rsquo;t my best meal ever. One mistake I did make, was taking a drink from the flight attendants which was some thick, corn based drink, possible Corn Potage. All I can assume is it&amp;rsquo;s an acquired taste.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/tokyo-from-a-plane.jpg" alt="Tokyo from a plane">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I managed to capture a cool picture of Tokyo from above, capturing the intense scale of the city.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="tokyo-first-days">Tokyo: First Days&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="day-0">Day 0&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Just after touching down, I took the JR Keikyū Airport Line and the Yamanote Line from the airport to Tokyo Station. I was already impressed with the quantity and quality of the intra-city transit by how easy it was to get on and off these trains.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/tokyo-station.jpg" alt="Tokyo Station">&lt;/p>
&lt;h6 id="tokyo-station">Tokyo Station&lt;/h6>
&lt;p>I decided to walk from the station to my hotel because after being placed in the center of Tokyo, I wanted to see as much as I could. This ended up being a great decision, not only did my route take my past the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tokyo_Imperial_Palace">Tokyo Imperial Palace&lt;/a>, I got to see it illuminated.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/palace-1.jpg" alt="Tokyo Imperial Palace, Illuminated at night">&lt;/p>
&lt;h6 id="tokyo-imperial-palace-illuminated-at-night">Tokyo Imperial Palace, Illuminated at night&lt;/h6>
&lt;p>After getting to the hotel I walked Shinjuku 3 Chome around a bit but was quite exhausted so after about 45 minutes, I retired to my capsule hotel.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/nine-hours.jpg" alt="My capsule hotel, 9Hours">&lt;/p>
&lt;h6 id="my-capsule-hotel-9hours">My capsule hotel, 9Hours&lt;/h6>
&lt;p>Day one involved a lot of walking, and because i&amp;rsquo;m some weird data horder, a year and a bit later I say I took 14,613 steps. I can also show you exactly on a map where I went. Obviously the data isnt perfect and there are some weird artifacts, but for the most part this is where I went.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/too-much.png" alt="My timeline for December 29th, 2018">&lt;/p>
&lt;h6 id="my-timeline-for-december-29th-2018">My timeline for December 29th, 2018&lt;/h6>
&lt;p>The day started off with me going from the hotel to Hanzomon Station, one again walking instead of taking transit as I personally find walking as the best way to experience a place. I could have taken the rail from my hotel to Shibuya but walking half allowed me to catch my first real sights of the city and some of the really cool architecture.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/merge-one.png" alt="Aquifer and Really cool building!">&lt;/p>
&lt;h6 id="aquifer-and-really-cool-building">Aquifer and Really cool building!&lt;/h6>
&lt;p>Day one was filled with exploring and getting comfortable with the sights and sounds of Tokyo. Wandering from the &lt;a href="https://www.gotokyo.org/en/spot/78/index.html">scramble crossing&lt;/a>, to &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Takeshita_Street">たけしたどり(Takeshita Dore)&lt;/a>, and finally visiting &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yoyogi_Park">代々木公園 (Yoyogi Park)&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/yoyogi.jpg" alt="Yoyogi park temple!">&lt;/p>
&lt;h6 id="yoyogi-park-temple">Yoyogi park temple!&lt;/h6>
&lt;p>The hightlight of my day was definity walking around these amazing shrines and torii gates. Once I was done around the harajuku area I ventured up to Shinjuku, definitely my favorite of the three areas of the city from the whole trip. I found that Shibuya was way too touristy and didn&amp;rsquo;t feel very authentic, while Shinjuku was more authentic. I also took my first a chance to visit a &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Don_Quijote_(store)">Don Quijote&lt;/a> while in Shinjuku which only made me wish they existed in North America.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/downtown-two.gif" alt="GIF of downtown.">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Day two was spent doing a lot of similar things to the first day, visiting Shibuya, Shinjuku, and Harajuku. With the main difference is on day 2, I got the chance to visit Akihabara. Now i&amp;rsquo;m not too into anime, but it&amp;rsquo;s awesome seeing all of the huge figure shops, the billboards, and 5 story tall arcades. This is where I spent a lot of my time while in Aki, and I mean a LOT. In particular I fell in love with a game called Ongeki, a rythem game with 3 distinct sets of controls.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/aki.png" alt="Akihabara">&lt;/p>
&lt;h6 id="akihabara">Akihabara&lt;/h6>
&lt;p>I actually managed to spend almost a whole day, wandering through old technology shops and arcades. Selling hundreds of classic Nintendo consoles, games, and accessories.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/consoles.jpg" alt="Old consoles for sale.">&lt;/p>
&lt;h6 id="mama-maglione">Mama Maglione&lt;/h6>
&lt;h2 id="tokyo-new-years-and-hatsumōde">Tokyo: New years and Hatsumōde&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>My next few days were quiet during the day and busy at night, I spend my days walking around, exploring &amp;lsquo;hole-in-the-wall&amp;rsquo; type places and eating good food. I spend new years with a group of people that I met on Line. A group of us stayed around downtown Shibuya while the rest went to club around the Odaiba area. All and all a very fun night spend with some great people.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/japan/new-years.jpg" alt="Friends!">&lt;/p>
&lt;h6 id="the-best-people">The best people.&lt;/h6>
&lt;p>Hatsumode is the New Years celeberation in Japan that is celebrated amongst families. It is defined as the first shrine visit of the year and is incredibly popular amongst Japanese. I was looking for a place to go, I debated visiting Meji Jingu shrine however I ended up taking a train, getting off at a random stop, and vising a shrine there.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://blog.brennan.sh/posts/japan-part-two/">Continue Reading&amp;hellip;&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>