<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on The mind of Brennan</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on The mind of Brennan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PtPMRR: Price to Performance Modified Round Robin.</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/ptpmrr-whitepage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/ptpmrr-whitepage/</guid><description>Multi-cloud distributed task scheduling for cost and QoS optimization Cloud computing offers the ability to provision resources as required on a per-task basis. Due to the growth of Cloud computing, there are many challenges faced today. One of these challenges is scheduling tasks to minimize cost in respect to runtime. Task scheduling is considered an NP hard problem with O(m*n) complexity when running n tasks on m resources.
In a multi-cloud scenario we still want to select the best resource to run a task on.</description></item><item><title>New Years 2019 in Japan: Part Two.</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/japan-part-two/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/japan-part-two/</guid><description>I spent New Years 2019 in Tokyo, Japan as a rather spur of the moment travel decision. While there I fell in love with the food and made some great friends. Now over a year later, Im finally writing something about it.</description></item><item><title>New Years 2019 in Japan: Part One.</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/japan-part-one/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/japan-part-one/</guid><description>I spent New Years 2019 in Tokyo, Japan as a rather spur of the moment travel decision. While there I fell in love with the food and made some great friends. Now over a year later, Im finally writing something about it.</description></item><item><title>Using Github Actions to Automate Build and Deploy.</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/gh-actions-automate-build-deploy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/gh-actions-automate-build-deploy/</guid><description>Github Actions are a relativey new feature that was put in place to help people run CI/CD workflows directly from Github Repos. In my opinion, if you host your code on Github, they are the cleanest and fastest free form of CI/CD out there today.</description></item><item><title>How I Automated With Ease Using Github Actions.</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/gh-actions-automation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/gh-actions-automation/</guid><description>About a week ago I decided to revamp my personal site and FINALLY get a working blog in order. Since you&amp;rsquo;re reading this obviously the blog half worked out! But as someone who has always had a relative interest in DevOps and more recently started putting that intesrest into motion, I thought I would use this opportunity to enhance my skills in CI/CD</description></item><item><title>My Facination with Micro-Infrastructure and Mini-Cities</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/micro-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.brennan.sh/blog/micro-infrastructure/</guid><description>Often I find it hard to describe some of my weirder fascinations and hobbies. For examplem I find geodetic markers, strange geographical artifacts, and the math that links them fascinating. Luckily for me, geodesy and geography have titles and are fairly easy to describe.</description></item></channel></rss>