<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>weird on 0x7CC</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/tags/weird/</link><description>Recent content in weird on 0x7CC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.brennan.sh/tags/weird/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My Facination with Micro-Infrastructure and Mini-Cities</title><link>https://blog.brennan.sh/posts/micro-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.brennan.sh/posts/micro-infrastructure/</guid><description>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#micro-infrastructure">Micro-Infrastructure&lt;/a>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#compact-living-spaces">Compact living spaces&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#mini-cities">Mini-Cities&lt;/a>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#kowloon-walled-city">Kowloon Walled City&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#univeristy-campuses">Univeristy Campuses&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#indoor-emulated-cities">Indoor emulated cities&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="#wrapping-it-up">Wrapping it up&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Often I find it hard to describe some of my weirder fascinations and hobbies. For examplem I find &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Survey_marker">geodetic markers&lt;/a>, strange geographical artifacts, and the math that links them fascinating. Luckily for me, geodesy and geography have titles and are fairly easy to describe. When I get giddy over the &lt;a href="https://ridgelineimages.com/maps/geodetic-datum-origin-japan/">geodetic datum origin of Japan&lt;/a>, it&amp;rsquo;s fairly easy to find more about it because there are keywords I can use to get hits on Google. However, not all of the things that excite me like geodesy are easy to describe.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="micro-infrastructure">Micro-Infrastructure&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/micro-infrastructure/image1.png" alt="Example of a micro-infrastructure setting">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This brings me to what I like to refer to as &amp;ldquo;Micro-Infrastructure&amp;rdquo;. I define Micro-Infrastructure (which I will henceforth refer to as M.I.) as any set of systems that looks to maximize the functionality or utility of a space, in particular a relatively small space to that of its surroundings. What I mean by this is an area of buildings (commercial and residential), infrastructure, and routing between these services. In the first image, along the left is a series of shops and residences, all of which are interconnected via paths on both sides and elongated halls down the middle. The scale of the surrounding buildings is hard to view in the picture I took so let me show you a zoomed-out view.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/micro-infrastructure/image2.png" alt="Overview of Shibuya">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The set of buildings in my first image exists a meer 2 blocks from the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shibuya_Station">second busiest train station in the world&lt;/a> and minutes from the world-famous &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shibuya_Crossing">Shibuya Crossing&lt;/a>. Having such a (relatively) self-sustaining ecosystem in the middle of a busy downtown core is the center of my fascination.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>While theoretically M.I. shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be specific to a region, I seem to find it&amp;rsquo;s most prevalent in eastern countries such as Japan, Singapore, India, and Taiwan. My best guess as to the cause of this is zoning laws. All of these countries either have unique zoning laws when it comes to mixed residential and commercial or have zoning laws that are weakly enforced. This being said, while I tend to be most fascinated with the eastern examples of M.I., there are a few edge cases that I want to touch upon that are fairly western that hit the same notes as the ones previously mentioned.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="compact-living-spaces">Compact living spaces&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/e1/8d/8c/e18d8c2b8a5f6e41b82345ade0d95b8b.jpg" alt="Tiny Homes">
The recent surge of tiny homes that manage to fit living, working, and eating quarters in a small space that is often sub-500sqft fascinates me in the same way that M.I. does. By doing the same thing that I define as M.I. on an individual scale, the innovations and efficiency of packing that much functionality into a small space is a fascinating case of optimization.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="mini-cities">Mini-Cities&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The concept and terminology of Mini-cities is not a new one, although the use of the term varies depending on who you ask. However, I do want to set the record straight. When I refer to a Mini-city, I do not mean a full-sized city that has been scaled down to an unusable size. I am more-so referring to a fully functioning city, complete with the means to self-sustain, that exists on a scale that is relatively smaller to a normal city or that exists within a full-sized city. Let me throw some examples your way.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="kowloon-walled-city">Kowloon Walled City&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/micro-infrastructure/image3.jpg" alt="Kowloon Walled City">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with the Kowloon Walled City, I would recommend reading up more about it after this as I will not be doing the scale of this project any justice. The Kowloon Walled City was a former Chinese military fort in Hong Kong following the Japanese occupation of Hong Kong. After the Japanese surrender in 1945, the fort became a location of refuge for citizens fleeing the Chinese Civil War. At its peak, the Kowloon Walled City had an estimated 33k people, a function municipal government, restaurants, clinics. Some units within the Kowloon Walled City even had electricity and plumbing, although this was significantly rarer.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="univeristy-campuses">Univeristy Campuses&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/micro-infrastructure/image4.jpg" alt="UBC">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Another example of what I would consider a mini-city is a typical university campus. For example, the University of British Columbia in Canada is a great example of a fully-sustainable city, technically within a city. However, one special thing about UBC is the campus is separated from the rest of the city by a large wooded area and actually requires a small drive (or longer bus/walk) to get to.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/micro-infrastructure/image5.png" alt="UBC Map">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>While this example isn&amp;rsquo;t entirely true, in most University Campuses in the western world, campus infrastructure can range from a clinic to a full hospital, with most even having their own method power generation. Residences provide places for students to live, there are restaurants so students can eat, and often students can find work on campus. Aside from import and exports these campuses can be fully sustainable on their own.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="indoor-emulated-cities">Indoor emulated cities&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Finally, an edge case I want to hit briefly is what I call &amp;ldquo;Emulated Cities&amp;rdquo;. I won&amp;rsquo;t describe these too much because they don&amp;rsquo;t fit the definition as they&amp;rsquo;re usually not functional, but ill provide a few small images to show my point.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://blog.brennan.sh/img/micro-infrastructure/image6.png" alt="&amp;ldquo;emulated cities&amp;rdquo;">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These are facilities that are modeled to look like cities however they tend to serve a secondary purpose, such as a retirement home, mall, or play-place for children.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="wrapping-it-up">Wrapping it up&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I hope I have done a moderate job of defining the two terms, Micro-Infrastructure and Mini-Cities, and I hope I have done a good job at convincing you why they fascinate me. In all honesty, this was just a long rant on something I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to explain formally. I hope I did a decent job of formalizing it to you and I hope this helps others put their fascinations into words. Not all hobbies are easy to explain and it&amp;rsquo;s nice to be able to get it all out and explain the niche, absurd things that fascinate me. Thanks for listening.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>